Stanislaw M. Ulam Papers 1916-1984 Mss.Ms.Coll.54
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Professional correspondence, 1932-1986, 15.5 Linear feet 33 boxes
  - Arnowitt, Richard (Box Series I-1)
    - See Ser.I, Desen, Stanley
  - Arsove, Maynard G, 1959 (Box Series I-1)
  - Artin, E., 1956; n.d. (Box Series I-1)
    telescope
  - Artin, Natascha, n.d. (Box Series I-1)
  - Artur, Csetényi, 1973 (Box Series I-1)
  - Ascher, Edgar, 1972 (Box Series I-1)
  - Ashenhurst, Robert L., 1971 (Box Series I-1)
  - Ashmore, Harry S., 1964-1967 (Box Series I-1)
    Encyclopedia Britannica
    Mathematics & Logic article
  - Asimov, Daniel, 1967 (Box Series I-1)
  - Askey, Dick, 1976 (Box Series I-1)
  - Astin, Allen V., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-1)
    National Academy of Sciences
  - Atiyah, Michael, 1972 (Box Series I-1)
    Princeton talk
  - Augenstein, Bruno W., 1963-1983 (Box Series I-1)
    wave mechanics
  - Aulicino, John V., 1976 (Box Series I-1)
  - Ault, J. Burchenal, 1983 (Box Series I-1)
  - Avula, Xavier J. R., 1981-1982 (Box Series I-1)
  - Ayres, W. L., 1945 (Box Series I-1)
  - Baade, W., 1949 (Box Series I-2)
  - Babai, L. (Box Series I-2)
    -See Hajnal, A.
  - Bacal, Jacob, 1976 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baclawski, Kenneth, 1973 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baer, Reinhold, 1948-1971 (Box Series I-2)
    endomorphisms
  - Bagby, Philip, 1940?-1951 (Box Series I-2)
    SMU job search, biology, physics
  - Baggett, Larry (Lawrence), 1967 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bailey, Daniel E., 1966 (Box Series I-2)
    SMU calendar
    -See also Ser.I, Manning, Thurston E.
  - Bailey, Herbert S., Jr., 1955-1956 (Box Series I-2)
    re: Coll. Of Math. Problems
    Princeton University Press
  - Bailey, J. A., 1964 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baird, Bridget, 1971-1979 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baker, Howard H., Jr., 1967 (Box Series I-2)
    Senate committee on tech. & human environment
    For originals, see Ser.I, Muskie, Edmund S.
  - Baker, William O., 1965 (Box Series I-2)
    Bell Telephone Laboratories
  - Bakowski, [Alois], n.d. (Box Series I-2)
    In Polish
  - Baldridge, Jack, n.d. (Box Series I-2)
  - Bales, Verna, 1965 (Box Series I-2)
  - Ball, B. J., 1966 (Box Series I-2)
    New Scottish Book
  - [Ball], B. L., 1976-1977 (Box Series I-2)
  - Ballen, Samuel B., 1976-1983 (Box Series I-2)
    corrections to Shatterer of Worlds
    Ulam, Alex[ander]
    -See also Ser.I, Strauss, Peter
  - Ballwag, R. A., 1962-1963 (Box Series I-2)
  - Banach, Stefan (1892-1945), 1937-1977; n.d. (Box Series I-2)
    Some in Polish
    Steinhaus speech
  - Banach, Stefan, Jr., 1960-1974 (Box Series I-2)
  - Barcellos, Anthony, 1979-1981 (Box Series I-2)
    Interview
  - Barell, John F., 1976 (Box Series I-2)
  - Barner, Martin, 1975 (Box Series I-2)
  - Barnes, J. C., 1961-1963 (Box Series I-2)
    Hycon, civil def., laser glass
  - Barres, Peter Marshall, 1981 (Box Series I-2)
  - Barrett, John H., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-2)
  - Barrett, Lida K., 1973 (Box Series I-2)
  - Barrows, Robert Guy, 1976 (Box Series I-2)
    Adventures film
  - Bartholomay, Anthony, 1960-1972 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bartlett, A. A., 1978-1983 (Box Series I-2)
    -See also Ser.I, Gamow, George
  - Bartoszynski, Robert (Box Series I-2)
    -See Ser.I, Olech, Czeslaw
  - Barut, Asim, 1966-1983;n.d. (Box Series I-2)
    Gamow lectures
  - Bass, Robert W., 1957 (Box Series I-2)
  - Basu, D., 1969 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bateman, P. T., 1965 (Box Series I-2)
    integers divisible by 3
    Hoolim, Haar
  - Batty, Peter, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-2)
    Film on H-bomb
  - Baumgartner, James E., 1969 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bauer, F. W., 1977 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bazley, Norman W., 1971-1972; n.d. (Box Series I-2)
    Pimbley, George
  - Beadles, [Don], 1977 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bebernes, Jerrold, 1967-1977 (Box Series I-2)
    Mate, Attila
  - Beck, J. I. (Mrs.), 1968 (Box Series I-2)
  - Beck, Patricia D., 1980-1981 (Box Series I-2)
  - Beckenbach, E. F., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-2)
    Math for engineer
  - Bednarek, A[l]. R. (Box Series I-2)
    - Folder #1, 1970-1975 (Box Series I-2)
      Aomic projective algebra
      Millsaps, K. T.
    - Folder #2, 1976-1983; n.d. (Box Series I-2)
  - Begle, E. G., 1956-1967 (Box Series I-2)
  - Behan, J. F., 1959 (Box Series I-2)
  - Belcher, P. F., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-2)
    Los Alamos security violations
    -See also Ser.I, Brillouin, Leon
  - Bell, Clifford, 1958-1959 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bell, George I., 1964-1977; n.d. (Box Series I-2)
    Biophysics, biomathematics
  - Bellman, Richard (Box Series I-2)
    - Folder #1, 1944-1966 (Box Series I-2)
      Probability, functional equat., learning process
      Birkhoff, Garrett
      Cairns, S. S.
      Lefschetz, S.
      Coll. of Math. Problems
    - Folder #2, 1967-1983 (Box Series I-2)
      Mathematical Biosciences jrnl.
    - Folder #3, n.d. (Box Series I-2)
      Life after WWII
  - Bello, Francis, 1964; n.d. (Box Series I-2)
    Genealogy, computers
  - Beltrami, Edward, 1960 (Box Series I-2)
  - Benbow, [?], 1942 (Box Series I-2)
    Army mathematics
  - BenDaniel, David J., 1980-1983 (Box Series I-2)
    Set theory
    See Mycielski, Jan
  - Benesch, Marie, 1940 (Box Series I-2)
    In German
  - Bennett, Albert B., Jr., 1977 (Box Series I-2)
  - Benson, Ann, 1976 (Box Series I-2)
  - Benson, Sidney W., 1976 (Box Series I-2)
  - Beraha, Sami, 1962-1968 (Box Series I-3)
    inversion of matrices
  - Berg, Murray, 1964 (Box Series I-3)
  - Berge, Claude, 1971-1981 (Box Series I-3)
    Deza, M.
    Las Vergnas, M.
    Rosenstiehl, P.
    See American Mathematical Monthly
  - Berger, Agnes, 1976 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bergman, George M., 1961 (Box Series I-3)
    Product automorphisms
  - Bergman, Stefan, 1955-1962 (Box Series I-3)
  - Berkeley, Edmund S., 1957 (Box Series I-3)
  - Berresford, Geoffrey C., 1978 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bers, Lipman, 1957-1983 (Box Series I-3)
  - Besombes, Gilles D., 1978-1981? (Box Series I-3)
  - Bethe, Hans (Box Series I-3)
    See Peierls, R. E.
  - Betts, A. W., 1946-1947 (Box Series I-3)
    Los Alamos housing, forms for employment, requests and badges
  - Beyer, Ann, 1976 (Box Series I-3)
  - Beyer, William A., 1955-1975; n.d. (Box Series I-3)
    visual hulls, difference equations
    See Smith, Temple F.
  - Bhargava, T. N., 1975-1976 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bharucha-Reid, A. T., 1960 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bialynicki-Birula, A. (Box Series I-3)
    See Piskorek, Adam
  - Bialynicki-Birula, Iwo, 1977 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bielski, Mark, 1979 (Box Series I-3)
    Gawlinska, Halina
  - Bing, R. H., 1948-1975 (Box Series I-3)
  - Birkhauser Boston, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box Series I-3)
    re: publication of The Scottish Book
    Albers, Donald J.
    Cabell, Stephanie
    Kellam-Scott, Barbara
    Klein, Lauren T.
    Klump, Will
    Peters, Klaus
  - Birkhoff, Garrett (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder #1, 1936-1952 (Box Series I-3)
      Los Alamos clearance, Carson Mark, poem on GB., AEC clearance, Harvard, American-Soviet Friendship Committee
      Everett, C. J.
      See Bellman, Richard
      See Borgese, Elizabeth Mann
      See Price, G. Baley
    - Folder #2, 1953-1956 (Box Series I-3)
      Hydrodynamics, jet calculations, Coll. of Math. Problems, Lebesque measure
      Pasta, John
    - Folder #3, 1957-1967 (Box Series I-3)
      Nomination to NAS, George Birkhoff prize, synthetic materials for computers, von Neumann article, hydrodynamics
      Burington, Richard S.
      McShane, E. James
      Price, G. Baley
      Tuve, Merle
      Walsh, Joseph L.
      Wigner, Eugene P.
    - Folder #4, 1968-1982 (Box Series I-3)
      On Heims' "John von Neumann and Norbert Weiner"
      Rota, Gian-Carlo
    - Folder #5, n.d. (Box Series I-3)
      Publications, Fourier series
  - Birkhoff, George D., 1936-1943 (Box Series I-3)
    Functional equations
  - Birnbaum, Z. William, 1969 (Box Series I-3)
    Zbyszek Lomnicki
  - Bishir, John, 1977 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bishop, P. W., 1967 (Box Series I-3)
    Fermi calculator
  - Bissinger, Barney, 1959 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blackwell, David, 1957; 1983 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blaker, Warren, 1965 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blakley, G. R., 1965 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bland, Robert G., 1980 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blank, A. A., 1960 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blass, Andreas, 1976 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blass, Bronislaw, 1969-1983; n.d. (Box Series I-3)
  - Blass, Piotr, 1981 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blattner, Meesa, 1977 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bledsoe, W. W., 1974 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blenkinsop, I. H., 1981 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bliven, Bruce, 1976 (Box Series I-3)
    Alexander Sach's visit to FDR
  - Blizard, John, 1977 (Box Series I-3)
  - Block, Henry W., 1970 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bloom, David M., 1969 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bloomfield, Bruce A., 1966 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blum, Gerard, 1973-1974 (Box Series I-3)
    re: Koestler's The Challange of Chance
  - Blum, Julius R., 1971 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blumberg, Stanley A., 1975 (Box Series I-3)
  - Boba, Antonio, 1959 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bobrow, Robert J., 1968 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bochner, Salomon, 1942; 1958; 1979 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bode, Hendrik W., 1946-1948 (Box Series I-4)
    Communication theory
  - Boehm, George A. W., 1958-1968 (Box Series I-4)
    Fortune article on computers, Mark Kac
    Fullen, Betty
  - Bogdan, Victor M., 1977-1978 (Box Series I-4)
    (Former name: Bogdanowicz, Witold M.)
  - Bohm, David, 1957 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bok, Derek, 1977 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bolling, W. C., 1967 (Box Series I-4)
  - Borgese, Elizabeth Mann (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder #1, 1964-1965 (Box Series I-4)
      Kac, Mark
      See Kac, Mark
    - Folder #2, 1966-1967 (Box Series I-4)
      Max Black's comments on article
      Black, Max
  - Borgmann, Carl W., 1958 (Box Series I-4)
  - Borowska, Zofja, 1977 (Box Series I-4)
  - Borsuk, Karol (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder #1, 1937-1959 (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder #2, 1960-1979 (Box Series I-4)
      Madison, WI., Weizmann Inst. lecture
    - Folder #3, 1980-1982; n.d. (Box Series I-4)
      Newspaper article by Borsuk
  - Borsuk, Zofia, 1982 (Box Series I-4)
    In French; on K. Borsuk's death
  - Borzymowski, Andrzej, 1983 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bott[?], Rick, 1982 (Box Series I-4)
  - Boulanger, Philippe, 1980 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bourgin, Richard, 1974 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bourgin, [?], 1942 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bouricius, Willard, 1957-1958 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bourne, Samuel, 1964-1974 (Box Series I-4)
    Neyman, Kura-towski, locally compact subgroups
  - Bowie, William S., 1964 (Box Series I-4)
  - Boyd, Constance D., 1974 (Box Series I-4)
    corrections to Copernicus article
  - Boyer, Keith (Box Series I-4)
    See Anderson, Clinton P.
  - Bozhko, N., 1966 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bradbury, Norris, 1946-1969 (Box Series I-4)
    industrial cooperation, abstract of SMU's Oak Ridge talk; consulting
    Critchfield, Charles L.
    Peters, Max S.
    See Gamow, George
    See Jarmie, Nelson
  - Brahana, Thomas, 1982 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brainin, Joseph, 1964 (Box Series I-4)
  - Braithwaite, Karl, 1981 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bram, Leila D., 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brandenburg, Betty, 1962-1965 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brant, Bruce Edward, 1979 (Box Series I-4)
    Audio book of Adventures, binary-quadenary, alternatives to Braille
  - Brase, Corinne, 1970 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brauer, Richard, 1941; 1957-1958; n.d. (Box Series I-4)
    John von Neumann article
  - Braun, Martin, 1974 (Box Series I-4)
    Mappings
  - Braverman, Max, 1967; 1970 (Box Series I-4)
  - Breil, Jean, 1982-1983 (Box Series I-4)
  - Breit, Gregory, 1948 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bremerman, H. J., 1967-1968 (Box Series I-4)
    Bio-mathematics
  - Bricker, [Betty], 1976 (Box Series I-4)
  - Briese, Franklin W., 1971 (Box Series I-4)
  - Briggs, G. B., 1956-1957 (Box Series I-4)
    IBM
  - Briggs, W[illiam] E., 1974 (Box Series I-4)
    See Norton, Karl K.
  - Brillouin, Leon (Box Series I-4)
    Some in French
    - Folder #1, 1947-1965 (Box Series I-4)
      Classification of docs., SMU notes, 1/4/51 letter
      Belcher, Philip F.
      Wheeler, John A.
    - Folder #2, n.d. (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder #3, n.d. (Box Series I-4)
  - Brinton, Crane, 1946-1957 (Box Series I-4)
    Harvard Society of Fellows
  - British Chess Magazine, 1960 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brittain, Donald, 1966 (Box Series I-4)
    Fermi film proj.
  - Brittin, Wesley, 1961; 1970-1972 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brockman, John, 1983 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brolley, J. E., 1958-1971 (Box Series I-4)
    LASL research program, Oppenheimer Mem.
  - Brooks, Harvey, 1941; 1973 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brosche, P[eter], 1967-1968 (Box Series I-4)
    Some in German
  - [Brossa?], Beryl, 1975 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brotzman, Donald G., 1970 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Harold, 1980 (Box Series I-4)
    Secretary of Defense
  - Brown, Harrison, 1966-1972 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Norman L., 1972-1974 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Randall J., 1975 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brownell, F. H., 1960-1961 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brownson, Helen L., 1957 (Box Series I-4)
    Mathematical notes on letter
  - Brueckler, Keith, 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brylewski, [Tom], 1976 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1978-1980 (Box Series I-4)
    White House reception, Poland
  - Buck, R. Creighton, 1971 (Box Series I-4)
    Chris Todd
  - Budrewicz, [?], 1973 (Box Series I-4)
    Series II Ulam, Françoise
  - [Buersching?], Margaret Beyer, 1976 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1969 (Box Series I-4)
    Wilson, J. S.
  - Bumcrot, Robert J., 1972 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bundy, McGeorge, 1965 (Box Series I-4)
    Special Asst. to the President for National Security
  - Burbidge, Geoffrey, 1963-1973 (Box Series I-4)
    Explosive phenomena and nucleosynthesis in stars & galaxies
    Burbidge, Margaret
  - Burbidge, Margaret, 1963-1964 (Box Series I-4)
    Burbidge, Geoffrey
  - Burgwin, Howard, 1964; 1967 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burington, Richard S., 1957-1960 (Box Series I-4)
    See Birkhoff, Garrett
    See Garabedian, Paul R.
  - Burks, Arthur W., 1961-1971 (Box Series I-4)
    Cellular automata
  - Burlage, [Diane], 1979 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burton, Victor M., 1967 (Box Series I-4)
  - Busemann, Herbert, 1942, 1944-1947 (Box Series I-4)
  - Busenberg, Stavros, 1977 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bussgang, Julian, 1946; 1958 (Box Series I-4)
    Zuckerbrot, Frank
  - Cade, J. A., 1966 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cahn, Anne H., 1970-1971 (Box Series I-5)
    re: thesis on the A.B.M.
  - Cairns, Stewart S., 1946; 1952 (Box Series I-5)
  - Calder, Nigel, 1965-1966 (Box Series I-5)
    New Scientist
  - Calderon, Alberto P., 1978-1979 (Box Series I-5)
  - Calkin, Mimi, n.d. (Box Series I-5)
  - Cambefort, J. L., 1979 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cameron, A. G. W., 1967 (Box Series I-5)
  - Campaigne, H., 1950 (Box Series I-5)
  - Campbell, Charles C., 1965 (Box Series I-5)
    Bath Tub Row houses
  - Campbell, Frank L., 1961 (Box Series I-5)
  - Campbell, Paul J., 1979 (Box Series I-5)
  - Campbell, Robert H., 1957 (Box Series I-5)
    Organiz. charts, Nevada Test Site, propulsion reactor designs
  - Canadian Journal of Mathematics, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-5)
    Heilbronn, H.
  - Canfield, Charles R., 1958 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cardus, David, 1965; 1976 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carley, J., 1978 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carlson, Bengt, 1978 (Box Series I-5)
    Carlson, Julia
    Murphy, Dan
    See Gordon, Martin B.
  - Carlson, Tim, 1979 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carr, John W., III, 1952 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carrier, George F., 1967; 1971 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carson, Ward W., n.d. (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, Ciel M., 1969 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, David L., 1961 (Box Series I-5)
    Air Force Space Study Committee
  - Carter, David S., 1956-1975 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, P[at], 1978 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, William J., 1976; 1980 (Box Series I-5)
  - Case, James H., 1967 (Box Series I-5)
    Computers
  - Case, Kenneth M., 1979 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cashwell, Edmond D., 1971; 1980 (Box Series I-5)
  - Casti, John L., 1971 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cater, Steven C., 1977 (Box Series I-5)
  - Catlett, Duane S., 1983 (Box Series I-5)
    LASL weapons orientation lectures
  - Cavender, James A., 1975-1979; n.d. (Box Series I-5)
  - Cech, E., 1958 (Box Series I-5)
  - Celestron Pacific, 1974; 1976 (Box Series I-5)
    Telescope; Tuthill, Roger W., Inc.; eyesight
  - Cenzer, Doug, 1978 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chaitlin, G. L., 1977 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chamberlin, E., 1959 (Box Series I-5)
  - Champlain, W. P., 1953 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chan, Arthur C. H., 1970 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chandrasekhar, S., 1957-1964 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chapin, Leverett A., 1976 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chapple, Eliot D., 1980 (Box Series I-5)
  - Charney, Jule, 1957-1958 (Box Series I-5)
    von Neumann and meteorology
  - Charpie, Robert A., 1961 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chase, Gary A., 1969 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chatelet, A., 1950 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chciuk, A., 1974 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cheatham, Thomas E., Jr., 1954 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cheded, L., 1983 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chein, Orin, 1975 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chenette, Eugene, 1974 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chevalley, C., 1947 (Box Series I-5)
    von Neumann integer conjecture
  - Chirikov, Boris, 1964-1968 (Box Series I-5)
    Stochasticity, ergodicity
  - Cholewicki, Victor, 1980-1981 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chowle, S., 1961? (Box Series I-5)
  - Christiansen, Peter L., 1982 (Box Series I-5)
  - Christie, Dan E., 1970 (Box Series I-5)
    Name mistyped as "Chirstie"
  - Chudnovsky, David, 1974-1980 (Box Series I-5)
    Name also spelled "Choodnovsky"
    Chudnovsky, Gregory
    Moishezon, Boris
  - Chudnovsky, Gregory (Box Series I-5)
    See Chudnovsky, David
  - Church, Alonzo, 1942-1951 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clancy, H. G., 1948 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clark, Jack, n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Cleaver, Frank L., 1974 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clements, George F., 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cody, Donald D., 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Daniel I. A., 1979 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, David M., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Leon W., 1955-1958; 1971 (Box Series I-6)
    National Science Foundation
    Rosenberg, Alex
  - Cohen, Michael, 1963; 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Paul J., 1964-1979 (Box Series I-6)
    George Polya
  - Cohen, Regina, 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Stanley, 1982 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohn, Harvey, 1960-1967 (Box Series I-6)
    nonlinear transformation
    See Stein, Paul
  - Coit, Catherine, 1970-1982; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Cole, Julian D., 1968 (Box Series I-6)
  - Coleman, S. J., 1972 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, Fred, 1966 (Box Series I-6)
    Restitution to SMU and Adam Ulam after WWII
  - Collins, Larry, 1980 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, R. E., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Colloquium Mathematicum, 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Colvin, Burt, 1951 (Box Series I-6)
    See American Mathematical Society
  - Combinatorial Theory, Journal of, 1968-1972 (Box Series I-6)
    Star, Z.
    Younger, D.
  - Comer, Steve, 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Computational Physics, Journal of, 1974 (Box Series I-6)
    Alder, Berni
  - Conant, Don, 1978 (Box Series I-6)
    Infinity; mathematical physics
  - Condon, Edward, 1966 (Box Series I-6)
  - Connolly, Joseph G., 1962 (Box Series I-6)
    Hycon Co.
  - Connolly, Lucie, 1957 (Box Series I-6)
  - Connolly, Michael, 1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conners, Edward A., 1979 (Box Series I-6)
  - Constantine, Charles M., 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Contopoulos, George, 1965-1970; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Conway, J. H., 1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conway, John B., 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cooke, Adeline B., 1978 (Box Series I-6)
    Photos of geometric drawings
  - Cool, Steven L., 1972-1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cooper, Leon, 1975-1977 (Box Series I-6)
    Patterns
  - Cooper, Ralph S., 1961; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
    Humor on neutrino bomb, and Columbus' scientific review committee
  - Cooney, James (Box Series I-6)
    See LeBaron, Robert--Press Conference
  - Copeland, Robert, 1980 (Box Series I-6)
  - Corbin, Lee, n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Corbridge, James N., 1975 (Box Series I-6)
  - Corliss, William R., 1964 (Box Series I-6)
  - Corner, George W., 1962-1963 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cotro-Manes, Patricia, 1977 (Box Series I-6)
    Frontiers of Mathematics
  - Courant, Richard, 1950-1969 (Box Series I-6)
    NYU computing facility, AEC
    Fahrney, D. S. (RAdm.)
  - Cowan, G. A., 1959; 1983 (Box Series I-6)
    Conf. on Project SANE (Scientific Applic. for Nucl. Explosions)
  - Cranefield, Paul, 1952 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cranga, Robert, 1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crawford, Bryce, 1979 (Box Series I-6)
  - Creech, Roger L., 1980 (Box Series I-6)
  - Creutz, E., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-6)
    Project ORION
    General Atomic
  - Crew, W. H., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-6)
    Minutes of LASL: Committee on Visiting Scientists, Committee on Foreign Travel
    See Susco, Dante V.
  - Critchfield, Charles, 1955; 1969 (Box Series I-6)
    See Bradbury, Norris
  - Crocker, Arthur W., 1960 (Box Series I-6)
    re: Ulam/Everett patent on nuclear propelled vehicle
  - Croft, H. C., 1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crouch, Ralph, 1961 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crowe, Lawson, 1969; 1973-1974 (Box Series I-6)
    Univ. of Colorado business
  - Cullinane, Steven H., 1976; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Curtis, Kent K., 1971 (Box Series I-6)
  - Curtiss, J. H., 1947-1948; 1958-1959 (Box Series I-6)
    Insitute of Numerical Analysis
  - Clancy, H. G., 1948 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clark, Jack, n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Cleaver, Frank L., 1974 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clements, George F., 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cody, Donald D., 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Daniel I. A., 1979 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, David M., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Leon W., 1955-1958; 1971 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Michael, 1963; 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Paul J., 1964-1979 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Regina, 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Stanley, 1982 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohn, Harvey, 1960-1967 (Box Series I-6)
  - Coit, Catherine, 1970-1982; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Cole, Julian D., 1968 (Box Series I-6)
  - Coleman, S. J., 1972 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, Fred, 1966 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, Larry, 1980 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, R. E., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Colloquium Mathematicum, 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Colvin, Burt, 1951 (Box Series I-6)
  - Combinatorial Theory, Journal of, 1968-1972 (Box Series I-6)
  - Comer, Steve, 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Computational Physics, Journal of, 1974 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conant, Don, 1978 (Box Series I-6)
  - Condon, Edward, 1966 (Box Series I-6)
  - Connolly, Joseph G., 1962 (Box Series I-6)
  - Connolly, Lucie, 1957 (Box Series I-6)
  - Connolly, Michael, 1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conners, Edward A., 1979 (Box Series I-6)
  - Constantine, Charles M., 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Contopoulos, George, 1965-1970; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Conway, J. H., 1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conway, John B., 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cooke, Adeline B., 1978 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cool, Steven L., 1972-1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cooper, Leon, 1975-1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cooper, Ralph S., 1961; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Cooney, James (Box Series I-6)
  - Copeland, Robert, 1980 (Box Series I-6)
  - Corbin, Lee, n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Corbridge, James N., 1975 (Box Series I-6)
  - Corliss, William R., 1964 (Box Series I-6)
  - Corner, George W., 1962-1963 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cotro-Manes, Patricia, 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Courant, Richard, 1950-1969 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cowan, G. A., 1959; 1983 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cranefield, Paul, 1952 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cranga, Robert, 1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crawford, Bryce, 1979 (Box Series I-6)
  - Creech, Roger L., 1980 (Box Series I-6)
  - Creutz, E., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crew, W. H., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-6)
  - Critchfield, Charles, 1955; 1969 (Box Series I-6)